/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bec2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-pieces-of-general-career-advice?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for the A2A. As a student, I might not have the most accurate answer, but I'm glad to help! I. Looking for a job 1. Fix your targets  I'm going to fast-forward over the part regarding \"how to find a job\",  talking about why it's important to know what you want from a job. Answer yourself to the following questions:  a) Money / free time Here I'm considering the two career opportunities you can choose, build a start-up and pursue becoming a millionaire / billionaire path but choose to be mostly caught up with your job or choose a simple job that won't stress you up so much and have more time for you family and hobbies. This is a hard decision. Most of the wealthy people sacrifice it all for the career and are the best at it. They are financially successful, have a great reputation and expres Continue Reading Thanks for the A2A. As a student, I might not have the most accurate answer, but I'm glad to help! I. Looking for a job 1. Fix your targets  I'm going to fast-forward over the part regarding \"how to find a job\",  talking about why it's important to know what you want from a job. Answer yourself to the following questions:  a) Money / free time Here I'm considering the two career opportunities you can choose, build a start-up and pursue becoming a millionaire / billionaire path but choose to be mostly caught up with your job or choose a simple job that won't stress you up so much and have more time for you family and hobbies. This is a hard decision. Most of the wealthy people sacrifice it all for the career and are the best at it. They are financially successful, have a great reputation and expres Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.115Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good pieces of general career advice? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bec4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-advice-for-a-future-software-developer?-",
    "answer" : "I am not a software developer, however, I do own and run an IT outsourcing company. I have spent around 20 years working with developers and I have seen countless of these talented developers grow their experience and also their pockets. There are plenty of good points and advice from this thread, but here are three major advice based on what I have seen.  Advanced Skill Set Once you’re there, there is no better way to improve your experience than to increase your skills. Master one tech language and be very good in executing it. Increasing your knowledge and experience leverage you from others and can help you get your dream project. An experienced background and knowledge on a tech language let your employer or client know that you are capable of handling more complex projects. This increas Continue Reading I am not a software developer, however, I do own and run an IT outsourcing company. I have spent around 20 years working with developers and I have seen countless of these talented developers grow their experience and also their pockets. There are plenty of good points and advice from this thread, but here are three major advice based on what I have seen.  Advanced Skill Set Once you’re there, there is no better way to improve your experience than to increase your skills. Master one tech language and be very good in executing it. Increasing your knowledge and experience leverage you from others and can help you get your dream project. An experienced background and knowledge on a tech language let your employer or client know that you are capable of handling more complex projects. This increas Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.775Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best career advice for a future software developer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bec6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-some-good-general-career-advice-for-a-mid-level-graphic-designer?-",
    "answer" : "Andrew Cohen What is your skillset and background beyond mid-level?   If you're a print designer I'd make the transition to web and interactive design as fast as possible. If you're fluent in web and still doing client work, I'd look for an awesome product/startup to work on and leave clients behind.If you're still in love with clients, I'd work on some of my own products on the side. Who knows what you might come across :)If you're already in the startup world...keep crushing it.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.780Z"),
    "question" : "What is some good general career advice for a mid-level graphic designer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bec8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-can-a-high-school-student-do-to-prepare-for-their-future-career?-",
    "answer" : "Sol A. Koppel, works at General ElectricAnswered 1 year ago · Author has 1.8K answers and 142.9K answer viewsWhat can a high school student do to prepare for their future career? Sol A. Koppel It was 1956 and I was just discharged from four years of service from the Marines. Didn’t have a clue on what I wanted to do. It was a much different world at that time. None of my friends went to college and a lot of them never finished high school. But, you could find employment and many companies along with technical trades would be willing to train you for a position with their firm. But, the people who really did well are the ones that continued to gain knowledge by getting a good education and getting a college degree. The New York Times was a very respected newspaper and they had many sections pertaining to just about all national and international events. On Sundays, they had a very large special section pertaining to job openings. While going through this section I noticed that ther Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.784Z"),
    "question" : "What can a high school student do to prepare for their future career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9beca"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-for-doing-scientific-research-in-general?-",
    "answer" : "Research as the name suggests is a repeated process. You have to keep on with the search until you come up with something that is out of the ordinary or no one in the world has found before. This is basically the goal of any scientific study. Given this premise, you might have understood that one thing which is most required is perseverance. This is going to help you overcome all the tough situations and keep you motivated. You will have to focus on a very specialized topic for several years. For this, you will need to undertake proper introspection to identify a field of study that you are really interested in. Most of the time it so happens that young graduates are so eager to take up research that they join any lab possible. Later, this leads to lot of conflicts resulting in frustration a Continue Reading Research as the name suggests is a repeated process. You have to keep on with the search until you come up with something that is out of the ordinary or no one in the world has found before. This is basically the goal of any scientific study. Given this premise, you might have understood that one thing which is most required is perseverance. This is going to help you overcome all the tough situations and keep you motivated. You will have to focus on a very specialized topic for several years. For this, you will need to undertake proper introspection to identify a field of study that you are really interested in. Most of the time it so happens that young graduates are so eager to take up research that they join any lab possible. Later, this leads to lot of conflicts resulting in frustration a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.843Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give for doing scientific research in general? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9becc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-pieces-of-general-career-advice-during-such-times?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.845Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good pieces of general career advice during such times? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bece"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-and-general-career-saving-advice?-",
    "answer" : "·Turn up, every day, on time, rested, dressed appropriately, and ready to work. ·Take some serious further education, early in your career (Degree, Professional qualification or equivalent) This will give you a boost in salary, open up other opportunities, and will give you something to fall back on. ·If you can, get someone else to pay for this period of study ( no debt, guaranteed job, and also make sure you study something that at least one employer values) ·Do your best at every job you get, every day. ·Expect your current job to end at some stage ·Always be prepared for your next step, when your current job ends ·Always be looking to learn new skills / gain new experiences ·Be prepared to be inconvenienced, take some pressure, work some extra hours to gain new experiences & skills. ·Have 3 mo Continue Reading ·Turn up, every day, on time, rested, dressed appropriately, and ready to work. ·Take some serious further education, early in your career (Degree, Professional qualification or equivalent) This will give you a boost in salary, open up other opportunities, and will give you something to fall back on. ·If you can, get someone else to pay for this period of study ( no debt, guaranteed job, and also make sure you study something that at least one employer values) ·Do your best at every job you get, every day. ·Expect your current job to end at some stage ·Always be prepared for your next step, when your current job ends ·Always be looking to learn new skills / gain new experiences ·Be prepared to be inconvenienced, take some pressure, work some extra hours to gain new experiences & skills. ·Have 3 mo Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.848Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good and general career saving advice? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bed0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-you-start-a-career-in-politics?-",
    "answer" : "The exact same way as for an average person to start a career in professional sports. Understand you are going to get steamrolled every single day for the rest of your life. Accept it philosophically. Be grateful for the learning opportunity and the chance to participate. Succesful people in politics are not average. They are really smart, educated, strong mentally and physically, as in healthy. My highest IQ score is 155. Some of the people I have met are smarter. Expect to face that kind of opponents. A lot of the people you meet will be less than half of that. Be careful of every word, as they will not understand things the way you mean it. If this will not discourage you, lets move forward. Learn to think before you speak, and then not speak unless its necessary. Learn to respect other peopl Continue Reading The exact same way as for an average person to start a career in professional sports. Understand you are going to get steamrolled every single day for the rest of your life. Accept it philosophically. Be grateful for the learning opportunity and the chance to participate. Succesful people in politics are not average. They are really smart, educated, strong mentally and physically, as in healthy. My highest IQ score is 155. Some of the people I have met are smarter. Expect to face that kind of opponents. A lot of the people you meet will be less than half of that. Be careful of every word, as they will not understand things the way you mean it. If this will not discourage you, lets move forward. Learn to think before you speak, and then not speak unless its necessary. Learn to respect other peopl Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.851Z"),
    "question" : "How do you start a career in politics? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bed2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-some-general-career-advice-you-want-give-to-a-person-who-has-just-completed-school?-",
    "answer" : "It is a good question. Generally ,when students get confused after school life that what they do ? Which career path is good? Which stream will get them success ? And suddenly they heard abt some successful career path CA,Engineering , medical (to be doctor) etc which hav great fame. Some students hav their childhood dream some of listen to parents n relativ,some go with friends or some go with flow. Well Students dont want to do that .It is very necessary tht this decision is v imp of our life n we hav to deal with this lifetime . We will serve tht passion lifetime n it will serve us .so we have to choose our interested ,our desirable field which be our long term partner happily . N we will enjoy that to do. We will Never regret in future for our decision of choosing career . So first of all Continue Reading It is a good question. Generally ,when students get confused after school life that what they do ? Which career path is good? Which stream will get them success ? And suddenly they heard abt some successful career path CA,Engineering , medical (to be doctor) etc which hav great fame. Some students hav their childhood dream some of listen to parents n relativ,some go with friends or some go with flow. Well Students dont want to do that .It is very necessary tht this decision is v imp of our life n we hav to deal with this lifetime . We will serve tht passion lifetime n it will serve us .so we have to choose our interested ,our desirable field which be our long term partner happily . N we will enjoy that to do. We will Never regret in future for our decision of choosing career . So first of all Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.854Z"),
    "question" : "What is some general career advice you want give to a person who has just completed school? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bed4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-wrong-to-ask-for-advice-on-changing-your-career-and-life-in-general-at-41?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.857Z"),
    "question" : "Is it wrong to ask for advice on changing your career and life in general at 41? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bed6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-universal-is-general-life-or-career-advice-considering-cultural-or-national-context?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Luke Amargo 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.864Z"),
    "question" : "How universal is general life or career advice considering cultural or national context? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9bed8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-pieces-of-general-career-advice-given-by-Robert-Kiyosaki?-",
    "answer" : "Below are some of the images which truly depicts the career advice by one of the top personal finance author Robert Kiyosaki. Let’s begin;         Do follow this advice and most importantly, implement them in your life. 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.866Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good pieces of general career advice given by Robert Kiyosaki? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603495fc0c817f0398f9beda"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-pieces-of-general-career-advice-after-engineering-in-2020?-",
    "answer" : "If you have CSE or IT related degree than do IT job. Learn Skills if from tier 3 college. Learn Machine Learning, Deep Learning, make project at them. If don’t want to sit in front of crap screen, 2–3 boxes of motherboard, then prepare for government jobs. Prepare for IAS, IPS (just study 6 hrs a day only for 1 year), give CDS, AFCAT. Trust me, defence life is best as compared to civil life. Don’t give GATE because CSE or IT have no use of it unless you want to do higher educations. Try jobs at Forest Department, this is very adventorous job. Do adventorous jobs, Apply in Railways. Don’t sit in front of 2–3 boxes for 10–15 years. But do whatever you want to do man. Apne mata pita ko khush rakhko. Thanks",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:24.869Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good pieces of general career advice after engineering in 2020? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603496050c817f0398f9bedc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-venues-to-give-career-advice-or-help-Muslims-to-improve-their-education-standard-in-general?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Zeeshan Siddiqui",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:43:33.195Z"),
    "question" : "What are the venues to give career advice or help Muslims to improve their education standard in general? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034962a0c817f0398f9bee6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-do-you-have-for-someone-joining-the-military?-",
    "answer" : "Look at these other answers and take heed. Remember that if you can make the cut in the first place, you are ahead of over 95% the rest of the population in the first place. Expect it to be alternating physically hard, emotionally jarring, (Un-PC) wrongly hilarious, and tediously boring. Especially do remember to keep positive, and steer clear of others who got in and now just want to bitch about it. (You can bitch, but some people seem to forget to get their job done with all the bitching). REALLY remember that you will probably only get one chance at some really amazing experiences (like working with foreign troops in foreign lands, going to Airborne [parachutist] school, etc), so try to take advantage. Try the food (everywhere)… Also be careful about where you try the food. Keep an open Continue Reading Look at these other answers and take heed. Remember that if you can make the cut in the first place, you are ahead of over 95% the rest of the population in the first place. Expect it to be alternating physically hard, emotionally jarring, (Un-PC) wrongly hilarious, and tediously boring. Especially do remember to keep positive, and steer clear of others who got in and now just want to bitch about it. (You can bitch, but some people seem to forget to get their job done with all the bitching). REALLY remember that you will probably only get one chance at some really amazing experiences (like working with foreign troops in foreign lands, going to Airborne [parachutist] school, etc), so try to take advantage. Try the food (everywhere)… Also be careful about where you try the food. Keep an open Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:44:10.339Z"),
    "question" : "What advice do you have for someone joining the military? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034963c0c817f0398f9beec"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-career-advice-after-a-BSc-in-general-from-IGNOU?-",
    "answer" : "You can get a Teacher job with B Ed Write Bank Clerk /PO exams You can be IAS with UPSC CSE You can get job under SSC GL exam",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:44:28.096Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best career advice after a BSc in general from IGNOU? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603496510c817f0398f9befc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-positive-advice-can-you-give-to-a-50-something-wanting-to-start-a-career-as-Python-developer-having-just-a-general-knowledge-of-IT-and-programming?-",
    "answer" : "Start with learning Python. Install Welcome to Python.org and install Intellij ide. I suggest to buy Python books on the amazon to see which books have the user highest ratings. I would buy books that would cover everything about Python. This includes general python knowledge, django web development, python data science applications, network programming, etc. Run python programs using cmd and ide. Pick simple examples from the websites and run them. Then, come up wit your own examples and run them. Create github account repository and add the code your wrote to that repository. The code will be the proof to the future employers that you've written code yourself. The books will be used as reference. Try to write code on each topic described in the book. Then, I recommend careerbooster resum Continue Reading Start with learning Python. Install Welcome to Python.org and install Intellij ide. I suggest to buy Python books on the amazon to see which books have the user highest ratings. I would buy books that would cover everything about Python. This includes general python knowledge, django web development, python data science applications, network programming, etc. Run python programs using cmd and ide. Pick simple examples from the websites and run them. Then, come up wit your own examples and run them. Create github account repository and add the code your wrote to that repository. The code will be the proof to the future employers that you've written code yourself. The books will be used as reference. Try to write code on each topic described in the book. Then, I recommend careerbooster resum Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:44:49.733Z"),
    "question" : "What positive advice can you give to a 50-something wanting to start a career as Python developer having just a general knowledge of IT and programming? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603496660c817f0398f9bf0b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-pieces-of-general-career-advice-in-the-wake-of-the-coronavirus-and-technology-shifting?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Janko Acimovic Mark Hager",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:45:10.905Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good pieces of general career advice in the wake of the coronavirus and technology shifting? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034968b0c817f0398f9bf1b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-advice-would-you-give-to-someone-who-wants-to-become-restaurant-general-manager?-",
    "answer" : "Show up on time all the time and maintain health so you won't need as many sick days. Chances are these two reasons alone will make you a major asset to an owner whom more than often cannot do the same.The MBA component of your skill set is going to serve you better than many. This is one component of culinary school you can learn from books as well as you could spending a lot of money to go to culinary school. Learn the idea of running a restaurant as a business.General management requires the service orientation of the best concierges with the marketing and people management skill of the best salespeople. Don't give soft skills short shrift, they are as much the bread and butter of the restaurant business as actual bread and butter.There are purveyors who will try to buy your influence oContinue Reading Show up on time all the time and maintain health so you won't need as many sick days. Chances are these two reasons alone will make you a major asset to an owner whom more than often cannot do the same.The MBA component of your skill set is going to serve you better than many. This is one component of culinary school you can learn from books as well as you could spending a lot of money to go to culinary school. Learn the idea of running a restaurant as a business.General management requires the service orientation of the best concierges with the marketing and people management skill of the best salespeople. Don't give soft skills short shrift, they are as much the bread and butter of the restaurant business as actual bread and butter.There are purveyors who will try to buy your influence oContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:45:47.726Z"),
    "question" : "What career advice would you give to someone who wants to become restaurant general manager? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603496e00c817f0398f9bf3c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-new-job-titles-will-be-in-demand-in-2020?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What new job titles will be in demand in 2020?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:47:12.044Z"),
    "question" : "What new job titles will be in demand in 2020? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603497050c817f0398f9bf4a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-someone-who-wants-to-pursue-your-field-of-work?-",
    "answer" : "I am a partner for a large advertising agency here is what I truly think about my industry right now. There are a number of problems: Women / minority ethnics are not in abundance at the senior levelMargin / cost pressureTechnology companies are stealing talentLow salariesAutomation risk of job declineClients bringing agency services in-houseThere are also a number of great things: As long as you end up on good clients you can do very interesting workVariety (multiple clients)Variety (via technology / possibilities / potential)Colleagues (both the best and worst thing)New ideas / innovationIf I was starting in the industry today as a graduate say 23–24 years old this would be my strategy right this second:- Learn to write really really really well- Spend all my time outside of work learning Continue Reading Continue Reading Colleen Farrelly",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:47:49.952Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to someone who wants to pursue your field of work? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034971d0c817f0398f9bf52"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-someone-pursuing-a-career-in-being-a-human-resources-assistant-or-pursuing-the-human-resources-pathway-in-general?-",
    "answer" : "Make sure you are 25 - 35 female and look hot. That’s the advice I was given, at the time I was 55 with a fresh HR diploma and looking for a career change. On a more professional note… Figure out what role you want then learn about it deeply. Once you learn about it don’t brag about it, just use the knowledge and wisdom to be the best you can be. Training Industrial relations Oh and research the companies in your area that do HR the best, learn from the others along the way then aim to get into the best company, less stress, better motivation, more respect. Melissa Makan",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:48:13.034Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to someone pursuing a career in being a human resources assistant or pursuing the human resources pathway in general? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034974e0c817f0398f9bf64"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-sort-of-topics-around-the-general-theme-of-career-advice-would-recent-marketing-graduates-be-interested-in?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:49:02.067Z"),
    "question" : "What sort of topics around the general theme of career advice would recent marketing graduates be interested in? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603497740c817f0398f9bf70"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-good-writing-tips?-",
    "answer" : "Shivani Reddy Formatting1. Do not enter two letter spaces between sentences. Use of two spaces is an obsolete convention based on typewriter technology and will mark you as out of touch. If editors or other potential employers or clients notice that you don’t know this simple fact, they may be skeptical about your writing skills before you’ve had a chance to impress them. 2. Take care that paragraphs are of varying reasonable length. Unusually short or long paragraphs are appropriate in moderation, but allowing a series of choppy paragraphs or laboriously long ones to remain in a final draft is unprofessional. 3. If you’re submitting a manuscript or other content for publication, do not format it with various fonts and other style features. Editors want to read good writing, not enjoy aesthetically pleas Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:49:40.827Z"),
    "question" : "What are some good writing tips? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603497980c817f0398f9bf7d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-your-advice-be-to-someone-starting-out-in-a-career-in-general-practice-after-your-own-journey?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:50:16.345Z"),
    "question" : "What would your advice be to someone starting out in a career in general practice after your own journey? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603497ab0c817f0398f9bf92"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-advice-would-you-give-a-16-year-old-who-has-ADHD-and-general-learning-disabilities?-",
    "answer" : "If you have a dream, follow it. Don’t ever think you won’t be able to achieve your dreams just because you aren’t like others that our society has deemed normal. ADHD can be a plus because it allows you look outside of the box. I like to say there is no box big enough to contain us. When you find yourself on your chosen path, don’t give up. I am ADD as well as my daughter plus she has a learning disability with language. She dropped out of school her senior year in high school but finally graduated from a satellite school. She’s now 28, attending community college but eventually wants a degree in English. So never give up and don’t let anyone try to force you into a direction you know is wrong for you",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:50:35.569Z"),
    "question" : "What career advice would you give a 16-year-old who has ADHD and general learning disabilities? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603498e80c817f0398f9c003"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Career-advice?-I-have-general-manager-experience-in-fast-food-with-no-other-education.-What-job-can-I-pursue-outside-of-the-food-industry?-I-know-I-can’t-work-in-food-forever.-",
    "answer" : "This is just my observation from my perch in the cockpit. I think it’s probably harder in the long run. First, in the U.S. it’s probably easier to be hired once you’ve reached the minimum requirements that the airline has established. There is a long history of discrimination against women and the cor (more)",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T05:55:52.705Z"),
    "question" : "Is it easy to become a female commercial pilot? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d8220c817f0398f9cf02"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-college-major-to-have?-",
    "answer" : "Sameer What undergraduate qualifications are available? The subject you choose will usually determine the type of qualification you'll be studying for. Bachelors degrees are the most popular undergraduate route into higher education, and they span the range of subject disciplines - from environmental sciences, health and psychology, to law, history and English literature. Most Bachelors degrees last from three to four years, with assessment made through a combination of written exams, assignments and group projects. In many cases, they'll include opportunities to spend a year abroad or in industry. Shorter courses also exist in the form of foundation degrees, the National Vocational Qualification (NVQ) and the Higher National Diploma (HND). If you're an aspiring social worker or engineer, you may be Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:25:38.579Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best college major to have? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d87b0c817f0398f9cf1c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-ways-to-do-content-marketing?-",
    "answer" : "Meenakshi Vashisht, Marketing and Sales Coordinator at Ishir (2013-present)Answered 6 years ago · Author has 594 answers and 395.8K answer viewsWhat are the best ways to do content marketing? Meenakshi Vashisht",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:27:07.751Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best ways to do content marketing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d8c50c817f0398f9cf36"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-life-advice-you-would-give?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the best life advice you would give?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:28:21.121Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best life advice you would give? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d8d70c817f0398f9cf3c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-advice-would-you-give-to-someone-who-wants-to-become-a-doctor?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What career advice would you give to someone who wants to become a doctor?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:28:39.777Z"),
    "question" : "What career advice would you give to someone who wants to become a doctor? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d8eb0c817f0398f9cf42"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-be-your-advice-for-teens?-",
    "answer" : "Since I myself is a teenager I guess I should list the advices that could be the best suited for all the teenagers...😉 Let's get started ! First and foremost Don't run for love until you are completely settled economically coz love can't buy FOOD...Life is just like a Metro Train ,we keep on changing the stations which are our different, different achievements and all the passengers we meet in between are the people we meet in our life , so what I meant to say is that Don't depend emotionally on a person , he or she may change his station when you want them the most…Looks actually doesn't matter at all, it may matter to some people but you know na we say that Exceptions are always there in life…Happiness depends upon the way we look at the situations , something good or bad happen all the tContinue Reading Since I myself is a teenager I guess I should list the advices that could be the best suited for all the teenagers...😉 Let's get started ! First and foremost Don't run for love until you are completely settled economically coz love can't buy FOOD...Life is just like a Metro Train ,we keep on changing the stations which are our different, different achievements and all the passengers we meet in between are the people we meet in our life , so what I meant to say is that Don't depend emotionally on a person , he or she may change his station when you want them the most…Looks actually doesn't matter at all, it may matter to some people but you know na we say that Exceptions are always there in life…Happiness depends upon the way we look at the situations , something good or bad happen all the tContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:28:59.429Z"),
    "question" : "What would be your advice for teens? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d9240c817f0398f9cf54"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-common-last-words-before-death?-",
    "answer" : "Shruti Bhanushali Everyone’s unique, Everyone's beginning was distinctive, Everyone’s Struggle Was Different, So does their endings were too.  Here are some famous last words by famous personalities:- Simón Bolívar: “How will I ever get out of this labyrinth?” (Truly we all wanna get out but there's only way for it; death.)François Rabelais: “I go to seek a great perhaps.”Thomas Alva Edison: “It's very beautiful over there”..(I don't know where there is, but I know it's somewhere, and I hope it's beautiful)Bob Marley: “Money can't buy life”..(He got that)Leonardo Da Vinci: “I have offended God and Mankind because my work did not reach the quality it should have”..( Epicness Overloaded!!)Ludwig Van Beethoen: “too bad, too bad, it's too late”.. (You wanted to die earlier?)Karl Marx: “Last words are fools who haven'Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:29:56.417Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most common last words before death? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d9480c817f0398f9cf61"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-one-piece-of-advice-you-would-give-to-anyone?-",
    "answer" : "I was coming back to Delhi in a train. The journey is long, it's 5 hours. The journey is not at all long because this amazing girl just got her seat right with me. It took me 3 hours to collect courage to talk. But before that she herself laid the cornerstone. She certainly wants something from me. Her : Where you going? Me : (I was wrong, she is talking selflessly) Delhi. Her : In case, I fall asleep, could you inform me when Faridabad station comes. Me : (I was right previously) : Will certainly do. Her : Actually it's too much Sun out there. I need to sleep. (Suddenly her phone rings). Her : (shouting over phone) What do you mean? Doesn't matter guests are there, ask her to sit down and eat. (Disconnects). Me :What came to pass? Her : The maid forgot her place and took a chair because a guest told h Continue Reading I was coming back to Delhi in a train. The journey is long, it's 5 hours. The journey is not at all long because this amazing girl just got her seat right with me. It took me 3 hours to collect courage to talk. But before that she herself laid the cornerstone. She certainly wants something from me. Her : Where you going? Me : (I was wrong, she is talking selflessly) Delhi. Her : In case, I fall asleep, could you inform me when Faridabad station comes. Me : (I was right previously) : Will certainly do. Her : Actually it's too much Sun out there. I need to sleep. (Suddenly her phone rings). Her : (shouting over phone) What do you mean? Doesn't matter guests are there, ask her to sit down and eat. (Disconnects). Me :What came to pass? Her : The maid forgot her place and took a chair because a guest told h Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:30:32.595Z"),
    "question" : "What is the one piece of advice you would give to anyone? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d9710c817f0398f9cf6f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-was-the-best-relationship-advice-you-ever-got?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What was the best relationship advice you ever got?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:31:13.536Z"),
    "question" : "What was the best relationship advice you ever got? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d9a00c817f0398f9cf7a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-your-best-advice-for-an-18-year-old?-",
    "answer" : "Tanmay Kapil, 10th-94% ICSE,12th-90% ISC, JEE 2019-94 percentileAnswered August 25, 2020What is your best advice for an 18-year old? Tanmay Kapil I'm just 20 right now but I think I am capable enough to answer this. I'm considering you are about to go for higher education.Having been through that stage and that age, I have come across a lot of things that taught me a lesson. This all made me realise that I made a few bad decisions but I learnt a lot from these mistakes. One the most important and the biggest advice (according to me) for a 18 yo would be to follow your passion. A lot of people say this but very few implement this. You will regret not following your passion at some stage even if you succeed in life. I took up engineering but an year later is when I realised it never was my passion. I did it because I was good at science and my parents wanted me to take up engineering since according to them, commerce and arts is what aContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:32:00.497Z"),
    "question" : "What is your best advice for an 18-year old? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d9b50c817f0398f9cf88"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-first-year-engineering-student?-",
    "answer" : "Ankit Sabinkar, worked at Research Associate at CognizantAnswered 3 years ago · Upvoted by Sushant Tiwari, Student at TCET , Kandivali, Mumbai (2017-present) · Author has 51 answers and 118.2K answer viewsWhat advice would you give to first year engineering student? Ankit Sabinkar What advice would you give to first year engineering student?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:32:21.022Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to first year engineering student? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034d9ed0c817f0398f9cf9a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-become-a-world-class-coder-in-under-three-years?-",
    "answer" : "Three years is more than enough to moderately excel in programming. As any skill, you will need lots of experience to truly excel in programming (some say 10,000 hours, about 5 years on a full time job) but in just one year you can create a really good piece of software and in three years you could be talking in code. Don't forget to ask during the whole process, places like StackOverflow are designed for this if you cannot find some specific community for your interests or if later on you are participating in a project that doesn't have a space for discussion (this rarely happens). And answer other people's questions anytime you can, you can learn by teaching. Leaving qualifications aside and focusing on knowledge itself (you will need qualifications for some jobs), the path to be a program Continue Reading Three years is more than enough to moderately excel in programming. As any skill, you will need lots of experience to truly excel in programming (some say 10,000 hours, about 5 years on a full time job) but in just one year you can create a really good piece of software and in three years you could be talking in code. Don't forget to ask during the whole process, places like StackOverflow are designed for this if you cannot find some specific community for your interests or if later on you are participating in a project that doesn't have a space for discussion (this rarely happens). And answer other people's questions anytime you can, you can learn by teaching. Leaving qualifications aside and focusing on knowledge itself (you will need qualifications for some jobs), the path to be a program Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:33:17.927Z"),
    "question" : "How can I become a world-class coder in under three years? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da000c817f0398f9cf9f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-like-to-give-to-Indian-girls?-",
    "answer" : "Ishitha Sivakumar You 1.Remove your Headphones for Sometime. Music may give you peaceful mind. But wearing headphones constantly may result in lot of health issues. 2. When you are sexually molested in public(bus train shops hotel so and so) Slap him in front of everyone .He will regret for what he did. You can save 100 girls from him by your action.  3.Give First priority to EDUCATION not to your BOYFRIEND. Don't ruin your life by forcing your parents to get admission in the same college where your boyfriend is studying. If you are sure he is your life and you are his life then you don't have to do all this. Relationship is not about mutual dependency. 4. Don't treat your mother as slave. Eat what is given dont throw the food on her face saying I don't want it . If you feel like having your favourite food requ Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:33:36.329Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you like to give to Indian girls? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da150c817f0398f9cfae"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-advice-for-a-software-developer-to-earn-a-higher-salary?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the best career advice for a software developer to earn a higher salary?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:33:57.147Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best career advice for a software developer to earn a higher salary? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da360c817f0398f9cfbb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-you-have-some-regrets-about-your-career?-",
    "answer" : "Well the biggest mistake I did was not get aware of all the career options. My father is a fruit seller who doesn’t know about studies or career. It was me who had to take right steps for me and I just followed the others. Most of my friends were doing Engineering so I also did it. Well There are lots of mistakes I did in my career… First: During 12th class (science stream) I was dating a so called girl friend which used me for her sake. Second: I didn’t know about AIEEE and anything other career options after my 12th Standard. Third: When My all friends were studying hard to get selected in IIT’s or NIT’s. I was finding a content writing job whose poster says “anybody can earn 20k per month by part time work. Fourth: When I didn’t get any college for engineering, I followed my friend as he was Continue Reading Well the biggest mistake I did was not get aware of all the career options. My father is a fruit seller who doesn’t know about studies or career. It was me who had to take right steps for me and I just followed the others. Most of my friends were doing Engineering so I also did it. Well There are lots of mistakes I did in my career… First: During 12th class (science stream) I was dating a so called girl friend which used me for her sake. Second: I didn’t know about AIEEE and anything other career options after my 12th Standard. Third: When My all friends were studying hard to get selected in IIT’s or NIT’s. I was finding a content writing job whose poster says “anybody can earn 20k per month by part time work. Fourth: When I didn’t get any college for engineering, I followed my friend as he was Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:34:30.004Z"),
    "question" : "Do you have some regrets about your career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da480c817f0398f9cfc3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-single-most-valuable-piece-of-advice-you-ever-received-that-proved-true-and-useful-time-and-time-again?-",
    "answer" : "You know you will find it STRANGE that I implemented this great piece of advice in my life BEFORE realizing that I had actually received it from . So in a way I kinda re-discovered it myself! STORY TIME:(skip the story if you really really need to pee) You must have heard the awesome Akbar-Birbal stories. I have too. I don’t remember this one exactly but once Akbar asked Birbal what is the secret of his quick wittiness. How does he come up with such brilliant solutions to things. To this Birbal replied that he makes use of whatsoever resources he can get at that moment. King Akbar could not agree to the solution was somehow offended by this . So to ‘test’ Birbal’s answer’s authenticity, a few days later he asked his men to loose a mad Elephant (let’s call the Elephant ‘Pongo’) on Birbal’s p Continue Reading You know you will find it STRANGE that I implemented this great piece of advice in my life BEFORE realizing that I had actually received it from . So in a way I kinda re-discovered it myself! STORY TIME:(skip the story if you really really need to pee) You must have heard the awesome Akbar-Birbal stories. I have too. I don’t remember this one exactly but once Akbar asked Birbal what is the secret of his quick wittiness. How does he come up with such brilliant solutions to things. To this Birbal replied that he makes use of whatsoever resources he can get at that moment. King Akbar could not agree to the solution was somehow offended by this . So to ‘test’ Birbal’s answer’s authenticity, a few days later he asked his men to loose a mad Elephant (let’s call the Elephant ‘Pongo’) on Birbal’s p Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:34:48.800Z"),
    "question" : "What is the single most valuable piece of advice you ever received that proved true and useful time and time again? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da710c817f0398f9cfd1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-a-great-platform-to-help-students-find-optimal-career-paths?-",
    "answer" : "Rose Garg, Observer. Thinker. WriterAnswered 5 years ago · Author has 104 answers and 70.7K answer viewsIs there a great platform to help students find optimal career paths? Rose Garg If there is one, I have not come across it yet. Personally I think it will be really hard for any platform to actually help a student find an optimal career path because for starters it is hard to tell whether a student will actually end up choosing it in the course of life and all it has to offer, irrespective of their interest/intelligence, etc.  I think it is best to either \"learn on the job\" and decide for yourself if you want to be in it for the long haul or if you want to change course. I have seen through my experience and those of others that many successful people usually end up doing things that they did not \"study.\" Being in the right job,  usually happens with time, people get wiser, they understand that to be in a career one must actually love doing it everyday.  However there a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:35:29.576Z"),
    "question" : "Is there a great platform to help students find optimal career paths? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da830c817f0398f9cfd8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-did-Stargate-SG1-manage-to-get-so-many-government-and-military-officials-to-appear-on-the-show?-",
    "answer" : "The short answer is “By asking nicely and listening to them when they gave advice.” Stargate SG1 approached the US Air Force for advice on how to accurately portray Air Force personnel early in their first season. They quickly had their own civilian Air Force Public Affairs liaison helping them. After that point the uniforms (other than the SG field uniforms) were correct and even changed as the real Air Force changed. For example, when Air Force space operations personnel began wearing blue flight suits as their duty uniform, so did the gate room staff. When they shifted to standard green flight suits, so did the gate room crew. When the Air Force changed the appearance of the space operations career field badge, the new badge showed up on uniforms in SG1 almost immediately. The writing sta Continue Reading The short answer is “By asking nicely and listening to them when they gave advice.” Stargate SG1 approached the US Air Force for advice on how to accurately portray Air Force personnel early in their first season. They quickly had their own civilian Air Force Public Affairs liaison helping them. After that point the uniforms (other than the SG field uniforms) were correct and even changed as the real Air Force changed. For example, when Air Force space operations personnel began wearing blue flight suits as their duty uniform, so did the gate room staff. When they shifted to standard green flight suits, so did the gate room crew. When the Air Force changed the appearance of the space operations career field badge, the new badge showed up on uniforms in SG1 almost immediately. The writing sta Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:35:47.445Z"),
    "question" : "How did Stargate SG1 manage to get so many government and military officials to appear on the show? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034da990c817f0398f9cfe9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-piece-of-advice-you-could-give-someone-about-life?-",
    "answer" : "“Be yourself everybody else is already taken”. I had read this quote on a good morning message and I liked it very much. Many a time we try to imitate others or be like someone else. Retain your individuality. Whether it is in your appearance, relationships or even writing on quora. Do what's best for you not because someone else is doing it. God has blessed each individual with the power to think. Use it. Don't blindly follow people. Even in marriage retain your individuality. You don't have to be an alter ego of your spouse.Keep away from alcohol, drugs and smoking. If you think you can drown your failures and sorrows in drinks and drugs, think again. Within a few days you will end up with a worse problem than you started with. Instead listen and help other people who are worse off than Continue Reading “Be yourself everybody else is already taken”. I had read this quote on a good morning message and I liked it very much. Many a time we try to imitate others or be like someone else. Retain your individuality. Whether it is in your appearance, relationships or even writing on quora. Do what's best for you not because someone else is doing it. God has blessed each individual with the power to think. Use it. Don't blindly follow people. Even in marriage retain your individuality. You don't have to be an alter ego of your spouse.Keep away from alcohol, drugs and smoking. If you think you can drown your failures and sorrows in drinks and drugs, think again. Within a few days you will end up with a worse problem than you started with. Instead listen and help other people who are worse off than Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:36:09.125Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best piece of advice you could give someone about life? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dae20c817f0398f9d009"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-you-have-any-advice-for-my-early-20s-life?-",
    "answer" : "1.DREAM: Dream about what you want to achieve, where you want to be in life in 5 years or 10 years down the line. Make sure you feel your dreams and feel overly satisfied by it. 2.SET GOALS: Start by setting easy goals like waking up early in the morning or excersing everyday. Get a hang of achieving your goals, maknig it your best habit. Set short term goals and long term goals. Short term goals can be studying for that difficult course which you always hated and excel in it.Long term goals can be what you want to do in your life. For example, if you want to be an entrepreneur, read about what you need to do to reach there, follow people who have been through that road, know what they did to reach there and prepare your own timeline or to-do list. 3.BELIEVE: This is the difference between p Continue Reading 1.DREAM: Dream about what you want to achieve, where you want to be in life in 5 years or 10 years down the line. Make sure you feel your dreams and feel overly satisfied by it. 2.SET GOALS: Start by setting easy goals like waking up early in the morning or excersing everyday. Get a hang of achieving your goals, maknig it your best habit. Set short term goals and long term goals. Short term goals can be studying for that difficult course which you always hated and excel in it.Long term goals can be what you want to do in your life. For example, if you want to be an entrepreneur, read about what you need to do to reach there, follow people who have been through that road, know what they did to reach there and prepare your own timeline or to-do list. 3.BELIEVE: This is the difference between p Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:37:22.576Z"),
    "question" : "Do you have any advice for my early 20s life? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034daf50c817f0398f9d010"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-a-17-year-old-male?-",
    "answer" : "Fine, I’ll bite. But since everyone who ever answered this question before me seems so determined to act as if they are characters in Raphael’s The School of Athens (see below)…  …I’m going to have to go in the opposite direction and tawk zero philosophy. So listen carefully, and if at any point of time you feel inclined to disagree with me, remember this: I am right and you are wrong. One. Don’t go to the gym and lift weights, especially above your head. You’re seventeen. You’re going to want to conform to your peer group. The most obvious aspect of conformity is the physical. There’s an ideal physical image that most males your age uphold. And there’s the fastest way to achieve that image. So you’re going to go to the gym and start lifting. Here’s my advice: don’t. It won’t get you the body y Continue Reading Fine, I’ll bite. But since everyone who ever answered this question before me seems so determined to act as if they are characters in Raphael’s The School of Athens (see below)…  …I’m going to have to go in the opposite direction and tawk zero philosophy. So listen carefully, and if at any point of time you feel inclined to disagree with me, remember this: I am right and you are wrong. One. Don’t go to the gym and lift weights, especially above your head. You’re seventeen. You’re going to want to conform to your peer group. The most obvious aspect of conformity is the physical. There’s an ideal physical image that most males your age uphold. And there’s the fastest way to achieve that image. So you’re going to go to the gym and start lifting. Here’s my advice: don’t. It won’t get you the body y Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:37:41.614Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give a 17-year-old male? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034db0b0c817f0398f9d019"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-like-to-give-to-a-teenager?-",
    "answer" : "My fight with lust and masturbation – Teenage story After thinking a lot, I decided to answer this question in open forum and I do not want to be anonymous, am writing this fearlessly as I could not get much freedom to express my views during my teens. .There is a quote “whatever is personal is universal “, hence I am sharing a short story of mine, separating in four different paragraphs. I saw more than 100+ answers to this question, but have not read a single answer with some intention. May be this answer might have duplicated, I do not know .But I would like to touch upon a very sensitive topic of masturbation and lust which troubled me a lot during my teenage. If possible, please do read until end. I tried to make real story short. First para describes about my curiosity/anxiety towards  Continue Reading My fight with lust and masturbation – Teenage story After thinking a lot, I decided to answer this question in open forum and I do not want to be anonymous, am writing this fearlessly as I could not get much freedom to express my views during my teens. .There is a quote “whatever is personal is universal “, hence I am sharing a short story of mine, separating in four different paragraphs. I saw more than 100+ answers to this question, but have not read a single answer with some intention. May be this answer might have duplicated, I do not know .But I would like to touch upon a very sensitive topic of masturbation and lust which troubled me a lot during my teenage. If possible, please do read until end. I tried to make real story short. First para describes about my curiosity/anxiety towards  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:38:03.605Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you like to give to a teenager? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034db210c817f0398f9d023"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-marriage-advice-you-would-give-to-a-newly-married-woman-to-make-her-marriage-last?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the best marriage advice you would give to a newly married woman to make her marriage last?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:38:25.357Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best marriage advice you would give to a newly married woman to make her marriage last? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034db5f0c817f0398f9d039"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-biggest-career-mistakes-to-avoid?-",
    "answer" : "1) Never think of yourself as indispensable, feel grateful that you have the opportunity to contribute - learn from organizations like Uber whose CEO had to leave. 2) Nobody is bigger than the organization and its goals. If you are not contributing, you might be a burden to the company. 3) Avoid negativity at the workplace and at all cost avoid gossiping - negative things bubble up very quickly, noise gets created and you will be found out sooner than later. In any case you are downgrading yourself as a person if you are the centre of such things. 4) Never ever speak ill of your team members if you do not mean them- if you have a problem, deal with them personally rather than bloating out on the floor. 5) If you are serving notice, do NOT stop working- keep things simple. Do NOT change your wor Continue Reading 1) Never think of yourself as indispensable, feel grateful that you have the opportunity to contribute - learn from organizations like Uber whose CEO had to leave. 2) Nobody is bigger than the organization and its goals. If you are not contributing, you might be a burden to the company. 3) Avoid negativity at the workplace and at all cost avoid gossiping - negative things bubble up very quickly, noise gets created and you will be found out sooner than later. In any case you are downgrading yourself as a person if you are the centre of such things. 4) Never ever speak ill of your team members if you do not mean them- if you have a problem, deal with them personally rather than bloating out on the floor. 5) If you are serving notice, do NOT stop working- keep things simple. Do NOT change your wor Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:39:27.438Z"),
    "question" : "What are the biggest career mistakes to avoid? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034db740c817f0398f9d041"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-best-life-tips?-",
    "answer" : "CAUTION: Read till the end or jump to next answer.It may hurt or offend your beliefs and thoughts.Read if you are 18+.1. Professional tip. Indian parents believe there are only 2 professions in the world which get's good money and respect. You guessed it right! Doctors and engineers. 85% of engineers opted engineering just because of their parent's pressure, society pressure, social status or inspired by 3 idiots. Engineering, Soft skills, Aptitude, Reasoning, Seminars and mock up interview. Aren't they preparing you to become a corporate slave? No one motivates you or trains you to become rich, but everyone trains you to be the slave. It's you, who should dig your own treasure. Do what you like not what your parents like you to do. You got the life and enjoy it. There are a lot of people, who ar Continue Reading CAUTION: Read till the end or jump to next answer.It may hurt or offend your beliefs and thoughts.Read if you are 18+.1. Professional tip. Indian parents believe there are only 2 professions in the world which get's good money and respect. You guessed it right! Doctors and engineers. 85% of engineers opted engineering just because of their parent's pressure, society pressure, social status or inspired by 3 idiots. Engineering, Soft skills, Aptitude, Reasoning, Seminars and mock up interview. Aren't they preparing you to become a corporate slave? No one motivates you or trains you to become rich, but everyone trains you to be the slave. It's you, who should dig your own treasure. Do what you like not what your parents like you to do. You got the life and enjoy it. There are a lot of people, who ar Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:39:48.862Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the best life tips? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034db890c817f0398f9d04b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-advice-your-mother-ever-gave-you?-Do-you-feel-it-has-benefited-you-as-an-adult?-",
    "answer" : "Remember your roots. After two years of my stay in the U.S, I came back for a visit to see my parents in India. Ours is an average middle-class household Indian family. I always used to fight for money for parties and to celebrate with friends when I was in my Bachelors degree. My parents provided me meagerly. Since my Dad is a central-government employee, I always used to think why doesn’t he provide me with any money, I thought a central government employee earns good. Never did I think about what he went through to pay for my education, my sister’s and run a family of four. So, after I went to the U.S for my education, I got a Graduate Assistant position in the University, which not only paid my entire fee, but also my daily expenses. That is the first time I started earning for myself. Af Continue Reading Remember your roots. After two years of my stay in the U.S, I came back for a visit to see my parents in India. Ours is an average middle-class household Indian family. I always used to fight for money for parties and to celebrate with friends when I was in my Bachelors degree. My parents provided me meagerly. Since my Dad is a central-government employee, I always used to think why doesn’t he provide me with any money, I thought a central government employee earns good. Never did I think about what he went through to pay for my education, my sister’s and run a family of four. So, after I went to the U.S for my education, I got a Graduate Assistant position in the University, which not only paid my entire fee, but also my daily expenses. That is the first time I started earning for myself. Af Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:40:09.831Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best advice your mother ever gave you? Do you feel it has benefited you as an adult? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034db9c0c817f0398f9d053"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-someone-who-is-about-to-start-a-PhD-program?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What advice would you give to someone who is about to start a PhD program?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:40:28.955Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to someone who is about to start a PhD program? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dbaf0c817f0398f9d05b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-most-important-thing-to-consider-when-choosing-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Nice question! I am just 17 and I choose my career and am working towards it. What people usually do when choosing a career is: Choose a career where they earn a lotChoose a career due to parents/peer pressureChoose a career because a friend choose it and so onI would say do not look into any of the above,. Most parents force childern to do what they say, but sometime you have to choose to go against them because this is your future and not theirs. However, according to me the most important thing to consider when choosing a career is “what interests you”. You have to choose a career which you like doing. Never decide because someone forced you to, take time and look at what interests you and career options related to your interests. This is what I think, most people choose careers where they  Continue Reading Nice question! I am just 17 and I choose my career and am working towards it. What people usually do when choosing a career is: Choose a career where they earn a lotChoose a career due to parents/peer pressureChoose a career because a friend choose it and so onI would say do not look into any of the above,. Most parents force childern to do what they say, but sometime you have to choose to go against them because this is your future and not theirs. However, according to me the most important thing to consider when choosing a career is “what interests you”. You have to choose a career which you like doing. Never decide because someone forced you to, take time and look at what interests you and career options related to your interests. This is what I think, most people choose careers where they  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:40:47.331Z"),
    "question" : "What is the most important thing to consider when choosing a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dbc00c817f0398f9d065"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-least-enjoyable-part-about-being-a-mathematics-professor?-",
    "answer" : "Mathieu Dutour Sikiric Job insecurity. An old buddy of mine once commented that the “old bargain” made with new academics was a trade where the employee gave up some potential earning capability (taking a lower salary than they might get in industry, perhaps as an engineer, and also delaying the effective start of their careers) and in return got unusually good job security (and a particularly interesting job I would say). It appears that this bargain is being undone in the name of efficiency and keeping the academic workforce in line, without much of a close examination of the effectiveness of the policy or the effect on scholarship. Many colleges and universities are taking the advice of pundits who recommend that they operate more like businesses. So now most of them spend much more on administration than befor Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:41:04.416Z"),
    "question" : "What is the least enjoyable part about being a mathematics professor? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dbd30c817f0398f9d06c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-a-few-unique-pieces-of-career-advice-that-nobody-ever-mentions?-",
    "answer" : "Mitchell Earl Lesson 1: Opportunity often wears a disguise Six weeks out from law school I was working an awesome job as an event photographer for an economics think tank. A few minutes before one of the events one of the emcees bet me I wouldn’t go on stage to introduce the next speaker. She was wrong. In the best announcer voice I could muster, I ran onto the stage and brought the house down. The speaker loved it. So much, in fact, that he came and found me after his presentation and struck up a conversation. We immediately hit it off and he posed a challenge to me in that first conversation. Little did I know, his challenge would ultimately lead me to skip law school, move across the country to join a startup, write a book and later launch a new venture with him. And to think it all started with a bet as sim Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:41:23.573Z"),
    "question" : "What are a few unique pieces of career advice that nobody ever mentions? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dbe90c817f0398f9d075"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-golden-advice-did-you-learn-in-your-life?-",
    "answer" : "Prakhar Malik, A shy guy who belongs in Neverland.Answered 9 months ago · Author has 259 answers and 1.3M answer viewsWhat golden advice did you learn in your life? Prakhar Malik Making your own decisions. Become independent.Never trust and/or judge someone's looks.Should never look for an easier option to achieve something.Drinking lots and lots AND lots of water.Always take some time out for yourself.Using hobbies to distract your mind off of things. It does not matter if you are bad at it. It does matter, if doing that makes you feel better.Avoid using laptop/phone in a dark room.Not believing everything you see/hear people preach.Sometimes taking risks is the only step in making your life better. You have the recipe, but are you too afraid to try it?Philosophical conversations may sound lame and daunting, but they can help you realise the things you had known all along, but were just too ignorant of them.Doing things in the present can make a big difference. PrContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:41:45.006Z"),
    "question" : "What golden advice did you learn in your life? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dc110c817f0398f9d089"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-a-tattoo-affect-a-policeman?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Does a tattoo affect a policeman?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:42:25.037Z"),
    "question" : "Does a tattoo affect a policeman? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dc360c817f0398f9d096"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-can-you-give-to-new-programmers?-",
    "answer" : "Quentin Lassalle My advice, with over 30+ years of programming under my belt would be as follows… First I would like to define a few things. For me a programmer is simply someone who has learned the syntax of a programming language and can then write lines of code in an editor, compile it and then run it. Nothing more than that. I can teach my mom and my grandma to become a programmer! Will they be good at it? Probably not. But they are still programmers. I think that what makes a great programmer is everything around the actual language itself. Which means if as a programmer you want to become great, highly respected, highly solicited ($$$) and valued. Which in turn will bring you the best projects and challenges. Which in turn should make you happy and proud … then you want to be an amazing software develo Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:43:02.213Z"),
    "question" : "What advice can you give to new programmers? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dc470c817f0398f9d09f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-much-does-an-MS-General-Surgeon-earn-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Sasanka Reddy Valid question indeed, I can't really comment how anyone else as a general surgeon is earning but I can share my experience so far. During my internship at Gandhi Hospital, the final of MBBS where you are posted in different clinical departments of the hospital to get a feel of how each system works, we were paid around INR 10,000 per month. 70 INR = 1 USD (approx.) During residency in General Surgery at Osmania general, we got an average of INR 25,000 per month over the next 3 years. As a senior resident again at Gandhi hospital, we received INR 45,000 per month for a period of 1 year. After a year of working as SR, you get offered around INR 75 to 90,000 in most places if you join as junior consultant / assistant professor. Some key issues common to all : (I’m not joking / exaggerating and mer Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:43:19.068Z"),
    "question" : "How much does an MS General Surgeon earn in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dc5b0c817f0398f9d0a7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-words-of-advice-that-you-would-give-to-youths-in-general?-",
    "answer" : "Before writing this answer, I would like to clear two things. That, Here I am assuming younsters as - falling between 16–28 years of age. [well 28–35 years are also youngsters, but they are more adults rather being young]. And this advice is for all irrespective of profession, background, region and religion, and country. Keep Your Youth in you Alive. Never let it die.Have a vision about your life, about your career, about your goal and preplan for it.Never Give Up on anything which you truly and whole-heartedly aspire for, till you get exhausted with all the possibilities.Work Hard was old rule, New Rule is to Work Smart.Always have a proper diet, and take Right food. But yeah , also have one or two cheat days only per month.Go for Walk, or jogging regularly. As 21st Century has made all theContinue Reading Before writing this answer, I would like to clear two things. That, Here I am assuming younsters as - falling between 16–28 years of age. [well 28–35 years are also youngsters, but they are more adults rather being young]. And this advice is for all irrespective of profession, background, region and religion, and country. Keep Your Youth in you Alive. Never let it die.Have a vision about your life, about your career, about your goal and preplan for it.Never Give Up on anything which you truly and whole-heartedly aspire for, till you get exhausted with all the possibilities.Work Hard was old rule, New Rule is to Work Smart.Always have a proper diet, and take Right food. But yeah , also have one or two cheat days only per month.Go for Walk, or jogging regularly. As 21st Century has made all theContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:43:39.555Z"),
    "question" : "What are some words of advice that you would give to youths in general? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dc700c817f0398f9d0ad"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-a-14-year-old?-",
    "answer" : "As a stand-alone version of some rather extensive commentary I gave to the answer by an Anonymous, namely Someone anonymous's answer to What advice would you give to a 14 year old?, and given all the mistakes I made at those very same years, I will have to say this. DO NOT CRY POOR - even if you ARE poor, by whatever standard your country uses to define a poverty line. “Crying poor” means basically dismissing any and every possibility to advance toward accomplishing something you would like to (such as learning, for example) because you think you don’t have enough money to do it (e.g. not possessing enough money to be able to afford expensive University level books and ignoring the fact that a public library may have an inter-library loan option.). Don’t fall for this trap - all it will do Continue Reading As a stand-alone version of some rather extensive commentary I gave to the answer by an Anonymous, namely Someone anonymous's answer to What advice would you give to a 14 year old?, and given all the mistakes I made at those very same years, I will have to say this. DO NOT CRY POOR - even if you ARE poor, by whatever standard your country uses to define a poverty line. “Crying poor” means basically dismissing any and every possibility to advance toward accomplishing something you would like to (such as learning, for example) because you think you don’t have enough money to do it (e.g. not possessing enough money to be able to afford expensive University level books and ignoring the fact that a public library may have an inter-library loan option.). Don’t fall for this trap - all it will do Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:44:00.039Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to a 14 year old? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dc950c817f0398f9d0bf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-tips-for-high-school?-",
    "answer" : "Here are 20+ high school tips, that I generated from my other similar high school tips: Don’t get involved in high school dramas. And I mean it. These high school dramas are not worth its value in 10, 20, or 30 years from now. They are relevant in the present, but irrelevant after a couple of days, weeks, months or later on. If you still care about the dramas, trust me nobody except you will care.Make some friends. Some of these friendships can make or break you. Some can last a lifetime. Make some friends in high school, and as the years go on, you will know who are your real friends.Not everyone is going to like you. I learned that the hard way in high school. You cannot please everyone, which includes your classmates and teachers. In life, people are going to hate you somehow. And that’sContinue Reading Here are 20+ high school tips, that I generated from my other similar high school tips: Don’t get involved in high school dramas. And I mean it. These high school dramas are not worth its value in 10, 20, or 30 years from now. They are relevant in the present, but irrelevant after a couple of days, weeks, months or later on. If you still care about the dramas, trust me nobody except you will care.Make some friends. Some of these friendships can make or break you. Some can last a lifetime. Make some friends in high school, and as the years go on, you will know who are your real friends.Not everyone is going to like you. I learned that the hard way in high school. You cannot please everyone, which includes your classmates and teachers. In life, people are going to hate you somehow. And that’sContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:44:37.514Z"),
    "question" : "What are some tips for high school? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dcbb0c817f0398f9d0ce"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-worst-advice-being-given-to-millennials?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the worst advice being given to millennials?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:45:15.128Z"),
    "question" : "What is the worst advice being given to millennials? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dccc0c817f0398f9d0d4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-you-reject-the-job-offer-that-you-already-accepted?-",
    "answer" : "You can do whatever you want in the sense that the company whose offer you already accepted will not take you to court or send hitmen after you for rescinding your acceptance. What is at stake here is your own self-credibility vs. the chance to work at your dream company immediately. Let’s say you rescind your job acceptance. In all reality, the worst that the company will do is blacklist you and the people involved in your hire will remember you as an unreliable person. This may or may not have a negative impact in your career, but would not be a huge issue in all probability. What is a much more important result of this decision is that you will know yourself to be an opportunistic person without credibility. Any of your promise in the future will have less value to yourself because you kn Continue Reading You can do whatever you want in the sense that the company whose offer you already accepted will not take you to court or send hitmen after you for rescinding your acceptance. What is at stake here is your own self-credibility vs. the chance to work at your dream company immediately. Let’s say you rescind your job acceptance. In all reality, the worst that the company will do is blacklist you and the people involved in your hire will remember you as an unreliable person. This may or may not have a negative impact in your career, but would not be a huge issue in all probability. What is a much more important result of this decision is that you will know yourself to be an opportunistic person without credibility. Any of your promise in the future will have less value to yourself because you kn Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:45:32.756Z"),
    "question" : "Can you reject the job offer that you already accepted? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dd020c817f0398f9d0e8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-you-wish-you-knew-before-becoming-a-software-engineer?-",
    "answer" : "Sol Rosenbaum, BS/MS MEng, PE, Founder www.TheEngineeringMentor.comAnswered 2 years ago · Author has 1.5K answers and 1.3M answer viewsWhat do you wish you knew before becoming a software engineer? Sol Rosenbaum I am not a software engineer, but I have mentored a lot of engineers throughout my 16+ years in the mechanical engineering world. I have taught them that having some “peripheral skills” are often more important than their actual technical skills. The following three skills are examples of these peripheral skills and are really important for all engineers that are getting closer to graduation to use for success in their engineering careers . . . Work on your network - Are you making solid connections with your professors and other students. Having a solid network will help you tremendously over your career. It can help with getting a job or even as a resource when you need help on a specific task.Too many engineers make the mistake of only building their network when they need to find a jobContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:46:26.525Z"),
    "question" : "What do you wish you knew before becoming a software engineer? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dd280c817f0398f9d0f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-your-18-year-old-self?-",
    "answer" : "(18 YO me) This question is probably the most stupid question ever. I’ll only see people who just complain and nag about their life. (22YO me) I wish I hadn’t wasted my time in stupid things. Darn! How immature I was! Now the 24YO me is realizing the essence and emotions of most of the answers here. Funny how life changes, sooner or later. TL;DR Before I start, I would like to tell you that I was passionate for Aeronautical Engineering. Whenever an aircraft used to fly, in a silent awe, watch that wonderful bird of metal rising in thin air which gives me a sense of satisfaction and pride of what mankind can be capable of achieving. I am even a patriot of my country, India. So I naturally had the tendency to either serve in Indian Armed force as an engineer or be the face “Modernized Aeronautic Continue Reading (18 YO me) This question is probably the most stupid question ever. I’ll only see people who just complain and nag about their life. (22YO me) I wish I hadn’t wasted my time in stupid things. Darn! How immature I was! Now the 24YO me is realizing the essence and emotions of most of the answers here. Funny how life changes, sooner or later. TL;DR Before I start, I would like to tell you that I was passionate for Aeronautical Engineering. Whenever an aircraft used to fly, in a silent awe, watch that wonderful bird of metal rising in thin air which gives me a sense of satisfaction and pride of what mankind can be capable of achieving. I am even a patriot of my country, India. So I naturally had the tendency to either serve in Indian Armed force as an engineer or be the face “Modernized Aeronautic Continue Reading I ignored this question.For days.But now i have finally decided to answer it. Couldn't help my urge to speak out.So bear with me and my stupid answer. As i am bad at writing. You will know how really bad i write. So apologies beforehand. Here are the few things i wish to share… The only important person in your life who can and will help out in your life is YOU. No matter how much idiotic or philosophical it may sound its actually true. Believe in yourself. Its actually what’s inside that matters.Than what’s outside.Everyone out there are flaunting only the best versions of themselves. What they show is not what they actually are. Dont judge a book by its cover. No one will flaunt their worst days. So stop cursing yourself for not having that so called happy life.Yes,having a smart phone is sContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:47:04.314Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to your 18-year-old self? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dd4f0c817f0398f9d10a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-advice-would-you-give-to-a-normal-Indian-boy?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What advice would you give to a normal Indian boy?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:47:43.039Z"),
    "question" : "What advice would you give to a normal Indian boy? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dd610c817f0398f9d10f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-advice-seems-easy-on-paper-but-is-difficult-in-practice?-",
    "answer" : "Adam Fayed This one:  Consider something that many people are passionate about: sport and music. Take tennis as a random example. Roger Federer has a net worth of about 450 million. Nadal, the Williams sisters and others also have high net worth. But let’s look at the earnings of the top 200–300 players - http://www.protennislive.com/posting/ramr/current_prize.pdf If you look at the current rankings, whilst there are some older players who are `past their sell-by date` but have high career rankings, there are many tennis players ranked 150–200–300 in the world who barely make any money. Remember too, the lower ranked players often pay for their own costs. If you think about it though, being ranked 200 in the world at something is very impression. There is surely 200 recruiters who are multi-millionaires. I Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:48:01.464Z"),
    "question" : "What career advice seems easy on paper but is difficult in practice? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034dd720c817f0398f9d11a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-tips-Brian-Bi-can-share-for-undergraduates?-",
    "answer" : "Brian Bi",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:48:18.307Z"),
    "question" : "What are some tips Brian Bi can share for undergraduates? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ddac0c817f0398f9d130"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-advice-that-college-students-never-hear?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the best advice that college students never hear?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:49:16.554Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best advice that college students never hear? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034de080c817f0398f9d14e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-of-the-best-kept-secrets-about-getting-ahead-in-your-career?-",
    "answer" : "My career (plastic welding engineering) is very narrow.  There are three college degree programs for welding engineering / technology in the united states.  The biggest and oldes program is at The Ohio State University.  My year, there were 28 bachelors graduates.  In the Welding Engineering department, there was one professor who taught on plastics, and every plastics class was an elective (not required to graduate).   When I started my Master's, my advisor had three graduate students.  One of them is now a professor at another major university, one didn't graduate, and one is me.  In the 10 years since then, one other student got a graduate degree in plastics from the OSU Welding Engineering department, he now works in the medical field.  On the one hand, this means I have very little com Continue Reading My career (plastic welding engineering) is very narrow.  There are three college degree programs for welding engineering / technology in the united states.  The biggest and oldes program is at The Ohio State University.  My year, there were 28 bachelors graduates.  In the Welding Engineering department, there was one professor who taught on plastics, and every plastics class was an elective (not required to graduate).   When I started my Master's, my advisor had three graduate students.  One of them is now a professor at another major university, one didn't graduate, and one is me.  In the 10 years since then, one other student got a graduate degree in plastics from the OSU Welding Engineering department, he now works in the medical field.  On the one hand, this means I have very little com Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T10:50:48.708Z"),
    "question" : "What are some of the best kept secrets about getting ahead in your career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}